aisle.co 2019-08-28

# Privacy Policy

Aisle is strongly committed to your right to privacy. This section covers Aisle's privacy policy that highlights how we handle personally identifiable information that Aisle collects when you are on our Website or App. Please read this privacy policy carefully. All information covered by Aisle's privacy policy will continue to be protected under Aisle's privacy policy irrespective of any change in your membership status in the future. By using the Aisle Website or App, you accept all practices described in this privacy policy.

In this Privacy Policy, your "Personal Data" means information or pieces of information that could allow you to be identified. We process your personal data for us to be able to carry out our contractual commitments towards you. We use this information to assist you in your search for a suitable partner in terms of age, gender, height, interests etc. In addition we process Personal Data to comply with legal obligations. We also process your Personal Data for allowing other users to view your profile on Aisle, conducting an analysis of your browsing pattern and history, and allowing our access, payment and storage business partners to process your Personal Data.

Sometimes we need your consent to process Personal Data, such as for sending you newsletters and promotions. Before you can become a user we also ask for your explicit consent so that we can:

  * Place tracking cookies
  * Process your profile information
  * Process data that you enter about your partner preferences
  * Process photographs of you
  * Process details of your work and interests
  * Process your bio and other textual content added to your profile
  * Process your geolocation
  * Offer you services mentioned in this Privacy Policy that require an act of consent from you

You have the right to withdraw your consent at any time for processing your location, however, this will not affect any of the prior processing of your Personal Data.

You will be asked to register before you can use Aisle. In the process, you will be asked for your name, email ID etc. After registering, you can create your personal Aisle account ("Your Account"). In this respect, you are invited to provide us with your name, pictures of you, a description of yourself, details about your interests, philosophy, work and basic information about yourself (such as your age, height, religion, ethnicity, place of residence etc). We will process these data.

You can create Your Account through Facebook or Linkedin Login. By using Facebook or Linkedin Login, you allow the platform to share with us the (personal) data you have shared with them – such as your name, email, gender, date of birth, pictures, likes, friend information etc. We will process these data.

Please note that in case of overdue payments, we will need to retain your email address and phone number for communication purposes.

Furthermore, we will process your IP address, login information, customer service history, time zone settings, device ID, browser language and - if you have given us explicit permission – your geolocation.

We will only share your Personal Data with other users, and only what is necessary to assess if another user could be interesting for you – which will be clarified below.

We will only disclose your Personal Data to third parties if there is a legal obligation to do so by a statutory authority from the appropriate jurisdiction. We do not sell your Personal Data to third parties.

**Data on Your Account:** Your Account will be visible to other users. Your first name will be your identity on our platform. The description of yourself, and basic information regarding yourself (such as age, height, profession etc) will be accessible on Your Account. Members of Aisle can perform targeted searches on the basis of age, religion and other information that users share on their accounts. Once you have created Your Account, the data you have shared with Facebook or Linkedin will also be linked to Your Account. If other users have also used Facebook Login and have enabled Facebook Folio, you can see which mutual connections you and other users have. We advise you to be careful with sharing information on Your Account with other users.

**Your login information:** We will process and store your login information to verify your identity to access Your Account.

**Your email address:** We do not share your email address with third parties.

**Your email address will be used to:** inform you of your membership status; notify you other relevant activity regarding Your Account; engage you with the application through newsletters and for troubleshooting.

**Your geolocation:** We will share your current location to make it insightful for our users who may live or work nearby. We will never share your zip code with other users of Aisle. You can choose to share your geolocation, which is necessary to see which other users of Aisle are nearby at any given moment. Your geolocation will be shared with other users who have shared their geolocation. Please note that we never share accurate geolocations with Aisle users – the accuracy is limited to 0.5 kilometers at the most.

**Your date of birth:** Your date of birth is used to calculate your age, which will be visible on Your Account.

**Photos you upload:** While creating Your Account, it is necessary to upload pictures of yourself and to select a display picture for your account. We may use an external face recognition tool and other techniques to select the best pictures for Your Account. This selection may be based on features like image quality, composition and authenticity. Images uploaded by you may be modified by us to make them more presentable on the platform. New pictures uploaded by you will be reviewed before they appear on Your Account. The pictures that you upload will be displayed to other users. Your Avatar or other photos may also be included in email messages from Aisle to other users, if Aisle considers you to be a good match with that user. Your Account, including pictures might be displayed on the homepage of Aisle for public viewing with your consent.

**Your chat messages and other written content:** Your chat messages are strictly confidential and is only processed in order to give you access to your chat-history. Please note that we do use filter software and techniques that notifies us of chat messages with inappropriate content (e.g. derogatory or aggressive language, or unlawful use of our platform for advertisements or link-building.) After such notification we reserve the right to erase the offensive content. This is applicable to other written content you post on Aisle such as on My Story and My Date Idea.

**Your customer service history:** If you contact our customer service team, we keep a record of your correspondence with us, in order to optimize our service for you.

**Non-personal data:** We may also process non-personal data whenever you use our website or app. This data may include your browser type and version, the type of your computer or mobile device and technical information about your means to connect to our Websites (such as your operating system and platform and the utilized internet service providers).

**Push notifications from Aisle:** If you have given us explicit permission, we will send you push notifications via our App to inform you about your membership status and to notify you of new messages you have received and other activity with regard to Your Account. We may also send you push notifications with suggestions of people you might like and other promotional material.

If you refer a friend to Aisle, you will send an email message, Whatsapp message, SMS, Messenger message to the contact details you submitted to us. We won't share these details with anyone else. By choosing to invite your friend to join Aisle you confirm that your friend is happy to receive the invitation. You also hereby agree to indemnify and hold Aisle harmless from all claims arising out of your messages to any person through Aisle. You must and will not use our invite friends feature to send spam.

We try our best to ensure that your Personal Data is protected and secure from unauthorized or unlawful access, alteration, disclosure, use or destruction. We encrypt our services using SSL, the data is accessible only through a secret password and digital signatures, and our employees only have access to your data on a need-to-know basis. Unfortunately, the transmission of information via the internet is not always completely secure. Although we take all reasonable measures, we cannot guarantee the security of the data you transmit to our Website or App; any transmission is at your own risk.

Your Personal Data is retained no longer than strictly necessary or as long as allowed by law, whichever is shorter. In the event that you have not logged in to your profile for five years, your Personal Data may be erased from our records. Of course, you can always contact our support team through your registered email address with a request to delete your data from our records.

We are constantly looking for new ways to improve Aisle and we may unilaterally update this Privacy Policy from time to time. When there is a significant change in this Privacy Policy, you will see a pop up in the app which you will have to accept before you can continue to use Aisle.

You personal data may be hosted by our storage partners in servers located in countries other than your country of residence.

You can also view, edit or delete your Personal Data by logging in to your Aisle account. To protect loss of data due to natural disasters and other such unforeseeable circumstances, we store your details as backup for a safety retention window of upto three years following account deletion. During this period, account information will be retained although the account will of course not be visible on Aisle anymore.

When you delete your account, your personal data is deleted after this retention window. We only retain your email address and phone number in order to be able to contact you with regard to payment matters. For internal use, we may store generic, non-personal data regarding your activity as a user (number of people invited, number of logins, term of your subscription, payment method, etc).

Aisle shall not collect data from minors. Should a Member lie about his/her date of birth, and particularly if he/she fraudulently claims to be over 18 years of age, the parents of the minor in question should inform Aisle of this by sending an e-mail to [team@aisle.co](mailto:team@aisle.co), requesting the data to be deleted. Aisle commits to deleting all data on the minor in question as soon as possible.

When registering, the Member expressly consents to his/her data being transmitted to Aisle service providers and subcontractors outside of the Member's country of residence, to let Aisle run statistical studies, support users, and if need be, host data processed by the Application.

Aisle guarantees that the transfers are made under conditions ensuring the confidentiality and security of the data and providing an adequate level of protection in compliance with regulations.

  * in the event that we sell or buy any business or assets, in which case we may disclose your personal information to the prospective seller or buyer of such business or assets
  * to identify, contact or bring legal action against you if you are violating our terms of use or other rules or if we believe you are causing injury or interference with the rights of users, the general public or Aisle
  * if we or substantially all of our assets are acquired by a third party, in which case personal information held by us will be a part of the transferred assets
  * if we are under a duty to disclose or share your personal information in order to comply with any legal obligation, or in order to enforce or apply our terms and other agreements or to protect our rights, property, or safety of our customers, or others

Aisle, the accompanying website and app are owned by Aisle Network Private Limited, 4, 1st Main Road, 2nd Stage, Domlur, Bangalore - 560071

We reserve the right, at our discretion, to make changes to the terms of use and privacy policy at any time. The most updated version is available on our App and Website at all times. Please check the terms of use and privacy policy periodically for changes as all modifications are effective upon publication. Continued use of the Aisle app and website after revision indicates the user’s acceptance of the terms of use and privacy policy.
